keybr.com 2012-11-21

# keybr.com - Privary Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At _keybr.com_ we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on–going operation of one of our services. 

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, _keybr.com_ collects non–personally–identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. _keybr.com’s_ purpose in collecting non–personally identifying information is to better understand how _keybr.com’s_ visitors use its website. From time to time, _keybr.com_ may release non–personally–identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

_keybr.com_ also collects potentially personally–identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. _keybr.com_ does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally–identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally–Identifying Information

Certain visitors to _keybr.com’s_ websites choose to interact with _keybr.com_ in ways that require _keybr.com_ to gather personally–identifying information. The amount and type of information that _keybr.com_ gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with _keybr.com_ are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, _keybr.com_ collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with _keybr.com_. _keybr.com_ does not disclose personally–identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally–identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website–related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

_keybr.com_ may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, _keybr.com_ may monitor the most popular pages on this site. _keybr.com_ may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, _keybr.com_ does not disclose personally–identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally–Identifying Information

_keybr.com_ discloses potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on _keybr.com_ s behalf or to provide services available at _keybr.com_ s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using _keybr.com’s_ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. _keybr.com_ will not rent or sell potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, _keybr.com_ discloses potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when _keybr.com_ believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of _keybr.com_ , third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an _keybr.com_ website and have supplied your email address, _keybr.com_ may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with whats going on with _keybr.com_ and our products. We primarily use our website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. _keybr.com_ takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. _keybr.com_ uses cookies to help _keybr.com_ identify and track visitors, their usage of _keybr.com_ website, and their website access preferences. _keybr.com_ visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using _keybr.com_ s websites, with the drawback that certain features of _keybr.com’s_ websites may not function properly, or you may not be granted access to parts of the website, without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, _keybr.com_ may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in _keybr.com’s_ sole discretion. _keybr.com_ encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
